No subtitles.
You're too smart! It's like...
What do you mean?
Wait a minute.
It's on the dot!
Oh!
Wow!
That's good! That's good!
Hello, everyone.
I'm Haruka Yamashita from Hyugaizaka 46.
I'm at Yuzawaya!
I'm at Yuzawaya.
It's my first time here.
It's a nice place with the sound of trains.
Why am I here?
Mizuki Yamashita is graduating.
I came to buy something.
Well, I'll tell you what I came to buy.
I'll tell you later.
I'll get right into it.
My name is Haruka Yamashita.
I wanted to give something to Mizuki Yamashita, who is related to Yamashita.
I'd like to enter Yuzawaya.
I'm Yamashita.
I'm...
I'd like to go look for ribbons.
I don't think I know if I'm going to make the menu when I hear the word "ribbon
I'll make an announcement.
I want to tell you already, and I want to tell you soon, that I want to make that bag, that ribbon bag, using ribbons.
So, from all these ribbons...
From among them...
I'd like to find a color that Mizuki would say is hers.
I'd like to find the color Mizuki is known for.
Look at this! It's like Joyful Love!
I wonder where it is.
Wow, here.
I'll take a picture.
What color is this?
Yamashita Quiz. What color is it?
Silver.
I think it's silver.
When I think of Mizuki Yamashita, I think of silver.
I got a silver one!
I'd like to make a bag with it.
But I don't know what kind of bag it will be. I don't know either.
It's a secret.
There is something else I want to make, so I want to go and buy it.
The material for that. I'm going to buy it.
What is it? Bravins.
I'm sure you've all made one before.
I'd like to make a gold holder.
That's why I'm here to buy it.
Yamashita Gundan.
Mizuki Yamashita from Sakurazaka 46.
Mizuki Yamashita of Sakurazaka 46 does crafts with us.
I wonder where that is.
We haven't talked much yet.
I've been nervous.
What are you going to make, Mizuki?
What? What should I call you?
Mr. Yamashita?
About me.
What would you call me, Ms. Shizuki?
It's a problem.
You only say "problem.
Well...
In my opinion
Haru haru kana.
I'm the type of person who doesn't care about age or anything.
I'm really happy if you call me whatever you like.
I mean, I'm really happy just to hear you call me by my name.
I'd like to go out for ramen with you too!
Let's talk about that.
I like tonkotsu (pork bone) ramen.
As I recall.
I like tonkotsu the best among all ramen noodles.
I want to go eat tonkotsu ramen!
Ah! There it is!
Prabang!
Plastic ramen
I'm going to use 0.3mm plastic vanes.
I'm going to draw pictures on it
I'm going to do it.
I feel like a kid again!
Plastic plate
I'm so happy!
Then I'd like to buy it.
I'm going to buy it!
I bought it right away!
Yamashita
I bought it!
I put a little time in the thumbnail style.
I would like to make it as soon as possible!
Let's go!
Goats Yamashita
Goats
Hi, I'm Arka Yamashita.
I'm Arka Yamashita.
Um...
I'm still...
Yuzuki-san and Mr. Yamashita-san are not here yet.
I'd like to introduce the products of Yuzawaya, which I just visited.
I'd like to open it right away.
Well, I'm going to make it, aren't I?
I'll do my best!
Shoo!
But you know, I've never made one before.
What I'm about to make.
It's your first time to make it.
First of all, this is silver.
I don't care if it's silver or whatever
I have purchased 36mm ribbon
Cut the ribbon in half.
Does it fit?
Yes, it fits.
And now...
Fold it first.
Wait a minute.
I'm overconfident in my dexterity.
I'm sure you'll be fine.
Let's do it together.
Oh, that's right.
But what do you mean?
Wait a minute.
The struggle started right away.
But halving it is the right thing to do.
Help!
No progress!
One more time.
Let's start from the beginning.
I'll start from here.
We've got to start from here.
From here.
Take this...
Cut it in half.
Fold it.
Stretch it out a little bit.
Here... here.
Here's the crumple.
Like this, like this.
How did I do that?
Wait a minute.
But I have a good feeling about it.
I did it! I did it!
I've made this kind of tied kelp before.
My grandma used to make them.
Oh, oh, stop!
Stop!
Use this, crochet hook.
Tropical? Oh, my...
Mmm-hmm.
I can do it.
Wait a minute.
Here it comes... here it comes... here it comes...
We'll do this forever.
I'll probably do this forever.
I can make this faster than Yamashita-san!
I can't wait!
You're kidding.
Good morning.
So cute.
Welcome.
Nice to meet you, I'm Yamashita
I'm Yamashita, too
I'm Yamashita.
I've just met Haruka Yamashita of Yamashita Hyugaizaka 46
I'm Yamashita, nice to meet you.
Have you made it yet?
I did.
Which was it?
It's going to be fun
I knew it!
I'd love to join you.
Thank you very much.
Okay, I'll take this one.
What's this?
So I have a lot of things I just bought.
I'd like to make some.
I'd like to make it, too.
By all means.
I'm sorry, I don't know where I stand.
I'm so nervous.
Please don't be nervous.
Thank you.
I knew it!
I've only brought out two.
I'm sure they'll come out in the future.
I'm hoping to make something related to Mizuki Yamashita this year.
Wow!
I bought a lot of them!
Wow, too much!
I hope it won't self-destruct.
It's too much!
Wow, something like that...
Wow, it's great!
Why?
I heard he's bright, cheerful and funny.
No, no, no...
How do you do?
Thank you.
That's why I wasn't too nervous today.
That's important in life, isn't it?
I don't know.
You seem to be having fun.
I'm having fun.
I'm so happy.
He's not the type of person you'd expect to see in a third-year student at Sakuraboko.
It's fun.
Yay!
I was thinking of making magnets out of magnetic clay.
Clay magnets.
Wait a minute.
You're going to put magnets on clay?
Can you put it on the fridge or something?
Yes, I can.
I bought this so that you can put it on your refrigerator.
That's very kind of you.
Thank you very much.
I will make it as soon as possible.
Yes, sir.
What are you going to say? At first.
A line?
Yes, sir.
I use "mata" for everything.
I'm out, I'm in, I'm in.
I'm done.
Oh, I'm...
Well, what am I?
What am I?
What about me?
Do you want to join us?
Yes, I'm in.
Yamashita has started.
Yes, by all means.
Yamashita started.
Good morning.
Hello everyone, I'm Yamashita.
Yamashita here.
Yamashita.
We're both Yamashita!
It's a farce, isn't it?
I'll be on the same page in an hour.
Really?
I'll do my best.
Yes, sir.
Starting.
Here we go.
Yes, sir.
Why should I call you?
Oh, of course.
Well, I'm stumped.
Okay, then.
Yes, sir.
Starting.
Can I use the nickname you guys call me?
Yes, sir.
Haruo.
You read it, don't you?
I've always had an image of you being called "big" or "HaruHaru".
I've never been called Haruo before.
Haruoh is what my friends in middle school and high school called me
I'll call you Haruoh san then
No, you don't have to call me "Ms.".
I'll call you Haruoharuharu
HaruHaru then.
HaruHaru was chosen.
Thank you very much.
The third term students call me Shi-chan or Kashi-chan.
Whichever you prefer.
Shi-chan.
Yes, please.
Shi-chan, right?
Shi-chan!
I'm so happy.
I'm so glad.
I've been wanting to call you.
Is it me?
Yes, it's me.
I'm glad to hear it.
I'm older than you.
How old are you?
I'm 21 this year.
I'm 20 this year, so I'm one older.
One?
Yes.
But you're not older than me.
Shi-chan looks older than me.
What's this calmness?
Yes.
Yes, it is.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
No, no, no, no. I'm really enjoying this.
Have we met? Have you met Mizuki?
I've met her.
I've met a few people here at the office.
The first is that you came to see the Shinshan thing.
We did that, didn't we?
Yes, we did.
We met when you came to see us.
You came to our office, didn't you?
He also came to Sakurazaka.
Is that right?
That's right.
He's very busy.
I'd like to talk a little about the Yamashita Corps.
I see.
I'm Haruka Yamashita, a member of Yamashita-san's corps.
I'm Haruka Yamashita of the Yamashita-san Corps.
I introduced myself.
He said he was very happy to hear that.
That's how I joined the Yamashita-san Corps.
Joined
Yes.
After that, you were able to introduce them?
Yes, I did.
So we've only just finished the initiation ceremony.
I see.
The initiation ceremony?
Yes.
I'm Yamashita, and we've just met and I've introduced myself.
Oh, I see.
I see.
I also happened to meet him at the company.
He gave me some bread and I ate it.
That's amazing.
You're already a member, aren't you?
A member?
Yes, I am.
I got the bread in the same way as the Kime Dumplings.
The dumplings are delicious!
Amazing!
But in the showroom
Um...
Showroom.
Mizuki talked to you in the showroom, right?
That's right, she was talking to us.
That's great.
I wonder if I can do it.
Have you ever made one before?
No, I haven't.
Is this your first time?
It's my first time.
Yes, it is.
ShiYuki can sew, right?
I do a little knitting, but it's just a hobby.
That's amazing.
I'm addicted to it.
I did for a while.
What? Have you made anything?
Flowers.
Like those drawstrings?
Yes.
You're the store owner, aren't you?
But everyone from the third term is still doing it.
What are you good at? Something I'm good at?
Sanshin? That's right.
You used to do that, right? I saw you do it.
The first time I saw you.
I thought it was cute.
Hina-ai?
I watched a little bit of it.
But I was just at the time of the unveiling of the 4th term students.
I hadn't even joined Sakurazaka yet.
I watched it in the school bathroom.
Every day at 12:00 p.m.
Thank you very much.
A guy named Yamashita came in with the same name as me.
What? I was like...
I was so surprised.
That's right.
It's a surprise when you have the same last name.
Maybe our ancestors are related.
Ancestors? Ancestor?
Ancestor? Ancestor?
Are you knitting the second half?
Yes, I'm knitting it.
So it's like you're just going to keep doing this?
I'm going to keep doing this and then I'm going to knit the rest.
A cord?
So that you can hang it on your shoulder.
What? Isn't that a bit difficult?
What? Do you want to play with it?
I've knitted a cover with something thicker.
That's great.
But it still made my shoulders stiff.
I did some stretching.
I'll try my best.
I see.
Tell me about it.
I'm sure you will.
I'm not sure.
Let me know if you get stuck.
I'm stuck.
Oh, now?
Where are you stuck?
I have to make a U-turn from here.
I see.
So this is the size of the base now, right?
I'll knit some more.
Yes, that's right.
Yes.
I'd like to knit a lot.
It's cute.
Yes?
Yes, sir.
I'm going to try knitting.
You're really starting to blush.
I see.
What is it?
Oh! What is this?
I'm struggling with something a little more difficult.
I'm struggling with a clay that somehow gets mixed with dust.
I don't know what to do with it.
Can't you get it off?
I'm trying to get rid of it with water.
I'm trying to do something with water, but...
Mizuki Yamashita is known for her rabbits.
I was hoping to make a bunny out of clay, so I'm working on it.
Oh?
Yes.
I'm a little worried that it won't turn out well.
You can do it.
Yes, I can.
I'm sure you can do it.
I'll do it.
Yes, I will.
You can do it, Shi-chan.
I'll do my best.
Hi.
Do you have any contact with Miki students?
I do.
Mr. Murayama.
Yes.
We've exchanged contact information.
That's new news.
Yes, that's new information.
That's right.
Something about Konishi Shiki...
Ah!
Konishi and Mr. Yamayama of Shiki in Hyuga are good friends, aren't they?
Oh, they are good friends.
Yes, they are.
That's great.
They get along really well.
I have the image that they get along really well.
That's right.
They have a similar vibe.
That's true.
You're both cool.
Yes, they are.
You and Hirao get along well.
Yes, we are.
Yes, they are.
Yes.
Listen to me carefully.
Yes, I do.
I'm listening.
Do you listen?
Yes, sir.
I'm here.
I'm talking to you.
Yes?
You and Kirari are getting along well today.
We went to a theme park.
We went to a theme park, right?
That's right.
We should get to know each other better.
I'd be happy if we could go somewhere together.
Yes, I'd like that too.
I love ramen.
Really? Really?
No way!
Did you say you love Tonkatsu Ramen the most?
Yes, I love it.
I'd like to go there.
Oh, I'd love to.
Really?
I'd like to go with you.
Yay! I'm so happy!
I'd love to know what kind of ramen stores you recommend.
With you?
I can only go to the ones on my list.
Wow, I love it!
Oh, really?
But it's been like 3 years.
I remember eating there about three years ago.
I'll say I love it.
Oh, I see.
Of course you do.
I eat it at least once a week.
That's great.
Yes.
We use honorifics, don't we? Yes, I've always thought so. I usually use honorifics.
Haruharu uses honorifics, too. Honorifics are nice.
I'm a junior...
We're the same.
So you and Kirari are honorifics?
I'd like to be as close to Kirari as you are.
I'm glad to hear it.
I'm struggling.
It starts like this and goes up like this.
Does it go down?
It can go either way, but it'll either go left or up.
If we continue to roll it in, I think we'll be okay.
Thank you for your help.
I'm glad you're helping me.
If I was alone, I wouldn't have been able to do it at all.
It's honorifics, honorifics, honorifics...
The most shocking thing for me was...
The most shocking thing to me was the violence of silence at the concert at ZOZO MARINE.
You performed "Violence of Silence" at ZOZO MARINE, didn't you?
At ZOZO MARINE, before that song started.
Before the song started, there was a solo cut, right?
And then the audience went silent and the penlights went out.
That was so cool!
That's right.
I got stuck in the front of the room and my eyes got stuck in the front of the room.
It was really cool.
I'm so happy!
The music, the music, the music, the music...
Yeah, the music.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I love it.
I was so happy to see them live.
Your performance was amazing.
Really?
I love your voice.
I love your voice, and the way you say your lines.
I like that.
Really?
He's really cool.
He's always giving me compliments.
Oh, my God, that's... that's... that's really nice.
Thank you.
How many hours does it take to learn that dance?
About three hours of choreography per song.
Yeah.
But I think I practiced Silence more than any other song in the third season.
I see.
It's the kind of song where you want to get the choreography just right, so the full song was already included in the music video.
What, since the music video?
Yeah, the music video itself is almost a dance cut.
I see.
Yeah, it was a lot of work.
That's great.
I'm glad.
Is it strenuous?
Yes, it is.
Of course it is.
But, Hinatazaka-san's...
Yeah.
Shinzan Momomi, I thought, flies really fast, doesn't it?
Ah, jumping
Yeah, that's tough too, isn't it?
Yeah, when it jumps
Yes, it is.
I feel like it takes a lot of energy out of me.
That's true.
But it makes you feel like you're having fun.
On the contrary.
That happens a lot, too.
I used to trampoline when I was little.
Trampolining?
Yes.
For fun?
No, that's not it.
It was more like what you're learning now, right?
Really?
Yeah. - Really?
For fun?
Yes, for fun.
Mihoko Ito's brother said that.
What's that?
A trampoline.
Yes, a trampoline.
It cost about 300 yen a time.
I see.
Crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle.
I'll stop if I talk.
It really does.
That's why it's concentration time.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
Uh-oh.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm so sick of this.
It's like...
It's like an expired carrot.
It was hard.
How did it happen so fast?
Wait a minute.
It's already taking shape.
So fast.
When I heard you were doing the bag.
I thought you were good at knitting so you could do it.
It's not that easy.
It's very difficult.
Not at all.
Mizuki left a lasting impression on me.
I was impressed with your story about the silver bag.
Ukizaka Kenkenchu.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
Yes.
But we're working on something that also pays respect.
I wonder if you'll notice.
I hope you'll notice.
Okay, everybody, I'd like to go to a different process now, but please wait a moment.
Back, the board.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Hang in there, hang in there.
Write.
Sorry.
Oh, here.
I'm sorry.
What do you like about it?
I really do.
The finished product. Here are the finished products.
How long did it take you to make that silver bag?
To put it compactly, about 3 days.
I really had to redo it many times.
So it may look completely different from the first one I knitted.
I knitted it myself.
Really?
You might think it's a very big bag.
Yes, it is.
It shrunk.
I think this one shrunk a little.
You're really good at this.
You can make a title on it.
It's cute.
I did this.
I finished the ribbon bag.
It's so cute. It's really cute.
Wait a minute. Could it be this?
I'm surprised you noticed.
Ah...
Te-te-te.
Tekk.
Huh?
Eh?
I closed with a totally heartless plastic bang.
It's cute. It's cute. Really cute.
Eh?
This is how I did it, right?
Yes, I did. I made this.
You're really good. That's amazing.
Really?
It's amazing.
I'm so happy. She said we made it together. I put it here.
That's great.
I wonder if I'm catching this.
You're so good.
Yes, very good.
Now, I'd like to lend you a present, Mr. Mizuki.
Okay.
I couldn't finish, so I need to stop by here and send them off.
Zoe, good. GDP makes a lot. Japan can also go get them.
You just finished the show.
Yes, sir.
How was it?
It was great.
It was really nice.
Yeah.
I'm impressed.
It was very moving.
But the stage was so cute.
Yeah, it was cute.
I was wondering if you guys had a chance to see it.
I made the video at the end too.
That's for sure.
I'm really happy.
I have a present full of memories.
I have it with me now.
I'm doing it after this, right?
Yes.
It's a one-shot show.
Finally.
I'm nervous.
I don't know what to do.
Mizuki was just talking.
I said we're going to fall in love.
At a time like this...
I want to be full of energy.
What should we say to her?
Thank you for your hard work.
Like this.
Three rounds of applause.
Three times?
I just did three claps.
I'm nervous.
I'm waiting.
How's it going?
I'm nervous.
Cute.
The first day of today's concert went well.
It seems two members of the Yamashita-kai are here to see us today.
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh....
I'm Yamashita from Porty Six.
I'm Yamashita of Karata Honteikutsu.
Thank you very much!
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you
Thank you for your hard work I made you a present if you like
Thank you.
What?
What's this?
Jadi!
What a toy!
What do you mean this isn't me?
I mean, I've lost it.
I'm glad you're here.
Don't you have any?
I can use it, thank you!
Yamashita Misato-san used to love rabbits.
I made the rabbit and the noodle man for the Seishun Festival.
I made a noodle man!
I have to do a quirk.
She knows the one from before.
I'm nervous because I love it so much
I'm so nervous
They're all magnets.
You can stick something on it and use it.
I'll put it on my refrigerator at home.
Thank you very much.
It'll be stylish
This is
I was notified of this by Nogizaka Kenshinchu's post.
I was impressed by what you said.
silver back
Oh, how difficult!
It was a very interesting time
When I wanted to make a bag
I thought, "If I say Mr. Mizuki, it must be silver.
I was interested in silver.
It's a little bit good.
No, it's not.
Respect 100.
I was 100 respectful.
It was 100 respect.
It's a lot prettier than the silver bag I had at the time.
I had at the time.
Yay!
Don't miss it.
This one.
Here.
Do this.
Like this.
This card...
Me and Shi-chan's
Oh, really!
Yamashita
You've really captured the characteristics!
We look so much alike!
A little subtle.
I...
I used this flower color.
I painted the flowers too much.
Oh, no.
It's true.
It's a nice color. I have to calm down.
If you put the three of them together, you'll get a certain someone.
What? What? What?
Te-te-te-te-te-te-te-te-te-te-te-te-te.
Hearto!
A heart!
That's amazing!
That's so cute.
Hearts!
It's like he's making hearts for me.
It's so funny.
Yeah, it is.
When the three of us get together
You can make hearts.
So cute!
Thank you.
I'm so happy.
Very Orysis!
I'm going to use this.
I always watch you two coach so much.
I'm looking forward to coaching these two.
I'll do my best
Use your heart at the end.
I'm so happy
Thank you so much.
Real
Real file
Wow.
Thank you for your hard work.
This is Umi Yamashita.
Thank you for watching!